[
  {
    "answer": "Yes. I like classical musics.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 844,
    "question": "Do you like musics",
    "qSentId": 843
  },
  {
    "answer": "Throwing yourself a party and get yourself a really nice gown.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 7,
    "question": "How many people do you absolutely, 100 percent trust?",
    "qSentId": 6
  },
  {
    "answer": "I don't do \"Bloody hell, I'm Oprah Winfrey.\"",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 19,
    "question": "Do you ever?",
    "qSentId": 18
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 35,
    "question": "Did you really?",
    "qSentId": 34
  },
  {
    "answer": "I would have to say it is really difficult for me still to wrap my brain around what all of that really means.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 49,
    "question": "What does it mean to you to actually have a network in your own name?",
    "qSentId": 48
  },
  {
    "answer": "We had a seduction through e-mail.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 80,
    "question": "Why are you pushing for me to do this?",
    "qSentId": 79
  },
  {
    "answer": "Probably five.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 83,
    "question": "How many people do you absolutely, 100 percent trust?",
    "qSentId": 82
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'm not naming them.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 85,
    "question": "Who would they be?",
    "qSentId": 84
  },
  {
    "answer": "You can guess.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 87,
    "question": "Can I guess?",
    "qSentId": 86
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 94,
    "question": "Are they people that we would know?",
    "qSentId": 93
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gayle didn't see it until we were actually in Australia.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 130,
    "question": "How did she react to what you were saying?",
    "qSentId": 129
  },
  {
    "answer": "Could you just touch me.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 145,
    "question": "Go along with the program?",
    "qSentId": 144
  },
  {
    "answer": "A newspaper is quite like a ship.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 163,
    "question": "Did you just say running a ship?",
    "qSentId": 162
  },
  {
    "answer": "There are two people I would never swear in front of.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 170,
    "question": "Did he just say?",
    "qSentId": 169
  },
  {
    "answer": "That's a good question, provocative question.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 179,
    "question": "Do like being famous?",
    "qSentId": 178
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cricket is fine.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 224,
    "question": "You don't like cricket?",
    "qSentId": 223
  },
  {
    "answer": "We went there.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 228,
    "question": "You were talking about Australia?",
    "qSentId": 227
  },
  {
    "answer": "Actually it was not piloted by John.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 240,
    "question": "How do you beat that?",
    "qSentId": 239
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, don't go there.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 255,
    "question": "Spiritual moment?",
    "qSentId": 254
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, I'm not a tough boss.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 267,
    "question": "Are you a tough boss?",
    "qSentId": 266
  },
  {
    "answer": "I suppose demanding.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 273,
    "question": "Might you define your definition of \"tough\"?",
    "qSentId": 272
  },
  {
    "answer": "I would say that I'm tough in that I'm always looking for the best in myself and I want you to also present that for yourself and for the overall goal that we share if you are working for me.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 284,
    "question": "Where would you say you're tough?",
    "qSentId": 283
  },
  {
    "answer": "One-hundred.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 308,
    "question": "One-hundred?",
    "qSentId": 307
  },
  {
    "answer": "It's OK.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 316,
    "question": "You don't like losing though, do you?",
    "qSentId": 315
  },
  {
    "answer": "More \"Piers Morgan Tonight\" coming up.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 337,
    "question": "What's been one of the most hurtful things you've had to hear or read about yourself?",
    "qSentId": 336
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'm the love brand.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 344,
    "question": "ORGAN: I know you hate this phrase but what is your brand do you think?",
    "qSentId": 343
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'm of love brand.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 347,
    "question": "Aren't we all, darling?",
    "qSentId": 346
  },
  {
    "answer": "That's really what it is.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 349,
    "question": "You like to shower love around?",
    "qSentId": 348
  },
  {
    "answer": "Boy, you're good.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 358,
    "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?",
    "qSentId": 357
  },
  {
    "answer": "Where it hurts your heart.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 371,
    "question": "By properly do you mean was it really love?",
    "qSentId": 370
  },
  {
    "answer": "Only two.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 379,
    "question": "You had your heart broken three times?",
    "qSentId": 378
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'm not naming them so they can call me up tomorrow.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 381,
    "question": "ORGAN: Who are they?",
    "qSentId": 380
  },
  {
    "answer": "When I look back to the relationship that I thought that really broke my heart, I was keeping a journal then.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 389,
    "question": "I was just curious -- as you say your brand is love, when it doesn't work and you love somebody passionately and it just doesn't happen for whatever reason, how did you feel about that?",
    "qSentId": 388
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes, I do.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 396,
    "question": "Do you really?",
    "qSentId": 395
  },
  {
    "answer": "I have them all.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 398,
    "question": "Do you have them all?",
    "qSentId": 397
  },
  {
    "answer": "I don't know.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 400,
    "question": "Why have you kept them?",
    "qSentId": 399
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, I haven't read them in years.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 403,
    "question": "Do you still read them?",
    "qSentId": 402
  },
  {
    "answer": "That's about it.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 411,
    "question": "What else have you got in there?",
    "qSentId": 410
  },
  {
    "answer": "I tell you who he reminds me of.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 414,
    "question": "INFREY: What about him?",
    "qSentId": 413
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Duke of Edinburgh, Prince Phillip.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 416,
    "question": "Who?",
    "qSentId": 415
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes, really.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 418,
    "question": "Oh, really?",
    "qSentId": 417
  },
  {
    "answer": "I think actually I had been betrayed by somebody in my family who had gone to the tabloids for, you know, $20,000 had sold me out.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 436,
    "question": "So when was that moment that you knew it was more than just a good relationship, it was special?",
    "qSentId": 435
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, I looked at him and thought here's something who is willing to stand in and stand up for you.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 449,
    "question": "You looked at him and thought, \"I love this man\"?",
    "qSentId": 448
  },
  {
    "answer": "INFREY: No because it's a waste of time, because I do the \"Oprah Show,\" \"excuse me, excuse you.\"",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 452,
    "question": "Do you ever argue?",
    "qSentId": 451
  },
  {
    "answer": "No.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 456,
    "question": "Really?",
    "qSentId": 455
  },
  {
    "answer": "No.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 458,
    "question": "Have you?",
    "qSentId": 457
  },
  {
    "answer": "No.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 463,
    "question": "You never had therapy?",
    "qSentId": 462
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, but I'm saying I've never had a day's therapy and God knows I could have used some.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 470,
    "question": "I need it?",
    "qSentId": 469
  },
  {
    "answer": "No.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 475,
    "question": "I just kind of assumed you would have at some stage had therapy?",
    "qSentId": 474
  },
  {
    "answer": "You.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 485,
    "question": "Who?",
    "qSentId": 484
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'm just not the marrying kind.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 534,
    "question": "Period?",
    "qSentId": 533
  },
  {
    "answer": "Oh, have a really nice party with the guest list and the seating on the table and all that.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 544,
    "question": "I mean, you know all those presents you could have?",
    "qSentId": 543
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, no, not in that, I wish I'd been a mother way.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 559,
    "question": "ORGAN: Do you ever wish you'd been a mother?",
    "qSentId": 558
  },
  {
    "answer": "No.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 573,
    "question": "Does any part of you ever wonder what would have happened if you'd had that child?",
    "qSentId": 572
  },
  {
    "answer": "Oh, for sure.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 579,
    "question": "Did you really?",
    "qSentId": 578
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, hid it.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 584,
    "question": "Did you ever tell your father that you had been pregnant?",
    "qSentId": 583
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, not -- you know, I did stupid things like, you know, drinking detergent and all that kind of crazy stuff that you do when you're trying to get attention, when you're really just trying to cry for help.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 595,
    "question": "Did you come close to doing that?",
    "qSentId": 594
  },
  {
    "answer": "I couldn't because I haven't paid enough attention to the curriculum to --",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 643,
    "question": "As someone who aspires to be a teacher -- and in many ways you are a teacher -- if you were giving an academic report on President Obama, what would you say, good and bad, pluses, minuses?",
    "qSentId": 642
  },
  {
    "answer": "I really do not.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 649,
    "question": "At all?",
    "qSentId": 648
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mm-hmm.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 661,
    "question": "Will you play a hypothetical game with me?",
    "qSentId": 660
  },
  {
    "answer": "My lane is evolving the consciousness of people everywhere, getting people to see the best of themselves and, therefore, the best in other people.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 673,
    "question": "Where's your lane?",
    "qSentId": 672
  },
  {
    "answer": "Not at all.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 680,
    "question": "No?",
    "qSentId": 679
  },
  {
    "answer": "INFREY: Well, I might be in a position to talk to -- to be an adviser.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 682,
    "question": "Who knows the American people better than you?",
    "qSentId": 681
  },
  {
    "answer": "Right now, 464 at Harpo.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 690,
    "question": "How many people do you employ?",
    "qSentId": 689
  },
  {
    "answer": "All the businesses.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 693,
    "question": "And it's a billion-dollar-plus business, right?",
    "qSentId": 692
  },
  {
    "answer": "I don't know the answer to that.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 701,
    "question": "How do you get America back on its feet?",
    "qSentId": 700
  },
  {
    "answer": "I don't write all of them now.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 715,
    "question": "You still write all the checks?",
    "qSentId": 714
  },
  {
    "answer": "I sign all the checks that are over 100,000 dollars, and that's a lot of checks.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 717,
    "question": "How many of them do you sign?",
    "qSentId": 716
  },
  {
    "answer": "INFREY: Oh, probably, you know, several hundred.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 720,
    "question": "How many?",
    "qSentId": 719
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 722,
    "question": "Of over 100,000 dollars each?",
    "qSentId": 721
  },
  {
    "answer": "The most pain I feel is -- and my accountants will tell you this.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 729,
    "question": "Do you feel pain?",
    "qSentId": 728
  },
  {
    "answer": "You're good.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 738,
    "question": "The one that's caused you most agony?",
    "qSentId": 737
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'm not sitting around counting it.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 747,
    "question": "Are you worth that?",
    "qSentId": 746
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because I already have counted it.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 752,
    "question": "So how do you know without counting it?",
    "qSentId": 751
  },
  {
    "answer": "No, I really don't, but I know it's more than 300 million dollars.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 758,
    "question": "Do you know how much?",
    "qSentId": 757
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes, of course.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 760,
    "question": "Really?",
    "qSentId": 759
  },
  {
    "answer": "It can certainly pave the way for it.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 769,
    "question": "Well, what do you think of the old saying, you know, money can't buy you happiness?",
    "qSentId": 768
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 781,
    "question": "Oprah, what is it you do best?",
    "qSentId": 780
  },
  {
    "answer": "I'm happier than I've ever been.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 793,
    "question": "Are you as happy now, do you think, as you've ever been?",
    "qSentId": 792
  },
  {
    "answer": "January 17.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 809,
    "question": "Oh, is it?",
    "qSentId": 808
  },
  {
    "answer": "INFREY: I would because I hold him in reverence.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 818,
    "question": "Why would you?",
    "qSentId": 817
  },
  {
    "answer": "I -- you have been surprising.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 841,
    "question": "How have I done?",
    "qSentId": 840
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yes, i like classical musics.",
    "docId": "110117pmt",
    "aSentId": 843,
    "question": "Do you like musics?",
    "qSentId": 842
  }
]